https://dailyillini.com/terms-of-use/

Rental Quicklist
More »
Terms of Use
Welcome to dailyillini.com (the ‘Website’) owned and operated by the Illini Media Company (‘Illini Media’). Please read these Terms of Use and the accompanying Privacy Policy carefully before using this Website and/or submitting any personal information that could identify you (including but not limited to name, address, telephone number and email address). By using this Website, you signify your agreement to these Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use and/or the Privacy Policy, do not use this Website.
Copyright and trademarks
The names and marks of ‘The Daily Illini’ and ‘dailyillini.com’ are the trademarks of Illini Media and are owned or licensed to Illini Media. All materials, including but not limited to images, audio and video clips, animation, diagrams, photographs and any and all information of any kind in any form (the ‘Materials’), incorporated into, published or otherwise exhibited on this Website are protected by copyright or other intellectual property rights and are owned and controlled by Illini Media or third parties who have licensed Illini Media the right to include the Materials in this Website. Any copying, reproducing, republishing, uploading, posting, modifying or transmission or distribution of any Materials is strictly prohibited and will be considered a violation of Illini Media’s intellectual property rights and could result in legal liability and/or criminal sanction.
Disclaimer
The Materials provided on this Website are for informational, educational and/or entertainment purposes only. Illini Media makes no warranties regarding the reliability, truthfulness, accuracy or completeness of any Materials. Unless otherwise stated expressly, any opinion, view or idea expressed in any article, review or story, or any content contributed or published by visitors in comments or otherwise disseminated or sent to Illini Media or others on or via this Website (‘Visitor Content’) is the author’s own and does not reflect the views of Illini Media or its affiliated and related entities, or its partners, sponsors, advertisers or content providers. Neither Illini Media, its affiliated and related entities, partners, advertisers, sponsors or content providers are liable to any person or entity whatsoever for any loss, damage, injury, liability, claim or any other cause of action of any kind arising from the use, dissemination of or reliance on any Materials or Visitor Content provided on this Website. You agree to use this Website entirely at your own risk. Illini Media and its affiliated and related entities, its partners, advertisers, sponsors and content providers disclaim all warranties, express or implied, including but not limited to implied warranties of merchantability and/or fitness for a particular purpose or that the Website will function error free or uninterrupted or that this Website or the servers that make it available for use are free of viruses or defects. Illini Media and its affiliated and related entities, its partners, advertisers, sponsors and content providers shall not be held liable for any information, services or products that are provided or offered by Websites that are linked to this Website. The links to other Websites are provided only as a convenience to you and do not constitute any endorsement of the linked Websites or any information, services or products that are provided or offered by the linked Websites. You agree that you use any linked Websites entirely at your own risk.
Visitor content and indemnification
Any Visitor Content provided by you to Illini Media, including comments, submissions, or other means, shall remain your property; however, by submitting, you grant Illini Media a non-revocable, non-exclusive right to publish, reproduce, disseminate, exhibit or otherwise distribute and use the Visitor Content in all media now known or hereafter devised. By submitting Visitor Content to the Website, you agree to represent and warrant that such Visitor Content shall not contain any libelous, defamatory, obscene, illegal, threatening or abusive materials and shall not infringe any intellectual property right or any other right of any person or entity and shall not breach any law. By visiting and using this Website, you signify your agreement to save Illini Media, its affiliated and related entities, its officers, directors and employees harmless from any and all damages, legal actions or causes of action that may now or hereinafter arise as a result of your use of the Website and your breach of these Terms of Use and/or any representations and warranties related to the Visitor Content. Illini Media monitors the use of its comments and any posted materials and reserves the right to remove any Visitor Content and block access to any visitor for any reason at its sole discretion.
Submission of online comments constitutes permission to use those comments in whole or in part in other media of the Illini Media Company without compensation.
Jurisdiction
This Website is owned and controlled by Illini Media, a nonprofit corporation incorporated under the laws of the state of Illinois and whose office is located in the city of Champaign. This Website is presented solely for informational, educational and entertainment purposes to visitors located in the United States of America. Neither Illini Media nor its affiliated or related entities make any representation, express or implied, that this Website will be available for use in or comply with the law of any country other than the United States of America. By using this Website, you agree that these Website Terms of Use and Privacy Policy shall be governed, construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the state of Illinois as it is applied to contracts entered into and performed entirely within such province and you submit to the jurisdiction of the courts of such province.
MOST READ
1Urbana announces emergency ban on indoor consumption of food, drink2Twenty ways to kill time: You don’t have to be bored in quarantine3Illinois uses defense, balanced scoring to thwart Duke 83-684UI bars Urbana students from COVID-19 testing on other two campuses5Illinois runs out of gas in second half, falls to Baylor 82-69
WEEKLY POLL
Are you excited for the holidays?No, COVID puts a damper on things
The Daily IlliniThe independent student newspaper at the University of Illinois since 1871
Submit Search
Search
The Daily Illini • © 2020 The Daily Illini • Privacy Policy •
FLEX WordPress Theme by SNO • Log in
CloseClose Modal Window
